The asteroid field is blindingly bright
A million sharp lasers cutting the night
The alarms on the console are flashing in red
A terrible static is filling my head
The sensory overload is breaching the heart
I'm losing the signal I'm feeling the pull
Close the blast shields, lock the heavy door I
don't wanna see the flashing lights anymore
Turn up the gravity, lower the sound Keep my
boots heavy right here on the ground Give me that
deep pressure Wrapping around A sanctuary
Built in the underground I need the weight, I
need the heavy hold To keep out the static, to
keep out the cold A protective atmosphere,
dense and secure
Give me that deep pressure Perfect and pure
The vacuum outside is chaotic and loud A
dangerous storm, a nebula cloud But inside this
cabin, the air is so thick The rhythmic
machinery is doing the trick The frequencies
drop to a comforting hum The panic is over, the
sanctuary has come
Close the blast shields, lock the heavy door I
don't wanna see the flashing lights anymore
Turn up the gravity, lower the sound Keep my
boots heavy right here on the ground Give me that
deep pressure Wrapping around A sanctuary
Built to lay underground I need the weight, I
need the heavy hold To keep out the static, to
keep out the cold A protective atmosphere,
dense and secure
Give me that deep pressure Perfect and pure
Give me that deep pressure Wrapping around A
sanctuary Built in the underground I need the
weight, I need the heavy hold To keep out the
static, to keep out the cold A protective
atmosphere, dense and secure
Give me that deep pressure Perfect and pure
Perfect and pure Turn up the gravity Keep me
secure
you